<?xml version="1.0"?>
<gameList>
	<game>
		<path>./Harvest Moon 64.z64</path>
		<name>Harvest Moon 64</name>
		<desc>Retire to the country for a new challenge in Harvest Moon 64. Hard work is rewarded as you struggle to bring prosperity back to a neglected farm. Work the land, pick up odd-jobs, and get to know the neighbors. Harvest Moon 64 has all the charm of the original Super Nintendo classic, plus many new surprises.

* Tons of new seasonal vegetables and fruits.
* Raise cows, chickens, and sheep.
* New items and gifts. Including tools that increase in power as you master them.
* One of town's five eligible women may prove to be the love of your life.
* Celebrate seasonal festivals with the nearby townsfolk.
* Enjoy local horse and dog racing.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/n64/Harvest Moon 64-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19991130T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Toybox</developer>
		<publisher>Natsume</publisher>
		<genre>Construction and Management Simulation</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Mario Party.z64</path>
		<name>Mario Party</name>
		<desc>Every game in the main series has a standard Party Mode in which up to four players play through a board, trying to collect as many stars as possible. In every turn, each player rolls a die and progresses on the board, which usually has branching paths. Coins are primarily earned by performing well in a minigame played at the end of each turn. On most boards, players earn stars by reaching a star space and purchasing a star for a certain amount of coins. The star space appears randomly on one of several pre-determined locations and moves every time a star is purchased, usually occupying a blue space.
Every Mario Party contains at least 50 to almost 110 minigames with a few different types. Four-player games are a free-for-all in which players compete individually. In 2-on-2 and 1-on-3 minigames, players compete as two groups, cooperating to win, even though they are still competing individually in the main game. Some minigames in Mario Party are 4-player co-op, even though it doesn't say it. In most situations, winners earn ten coins each.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/n64/Mario Party-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19990208T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Hudson Entertainment, Inc.</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Adventure, Puzzle, Strategy, Family</genre>
		<players>4</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Paper Mario (USA).z64</path>
		<name>Paper Mario</name>
		<desc>Mario pals around in an all-new action adventure! Mario's back in his first adventure since Super Mario 64, and this time, Bowser's bent on preventing a storybook ending. When Princess Peach is kidnapped, Mario plots to rescue the seven Star Spirits and rid the Mushroom Kingdom of Koopa's cruel cohorts. As he travels from the tropical jungles of Lavalava Island to the frosty heights of Shiver Mountain, he'll meet up with seven all-new companions... and he'll need help from each one or there'll be no happily ever after.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/n64/Paper Mario (USA)-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20010205T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Intelligent Systems Co., Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Role-Playing</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Quest 64 (USA).z64</path>
		<name>Quest 64</name>
		<desc>Celtland has been cast into chaos by the theft of Eletale's Book. This mystical volume contains the secrets of the Spirit Tamers. Control Brian, a magician's apprentice, as he explores the expansive countryside and villages on his quest. If he does not reclaim the book, the Kingdom of Celtland will be cast into darkness forever.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/n64/Quest 64 (USA)-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19980611T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Imagineer</developer>
		<publisher>THQ</publisher>
		<genre>Role-Playing</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./South Park (USA).z64</path>
		<name>South Park</name>
		<desc>Single player takes the form of a "Story" mode divided into five episodes and fifteen linear levels. The player will face weak minions (which change based on the episode), plus occasional sub-bosses which will try to escape into town. The final level is devoted to a unique boss fight. Players use quirky weapons ranging from infinite yellow snowballs to cow launchers and toxic Terrance and Phillip dolls. Every weapon has a secondary fire, and players switch between the four main characters when they switch weapons - each of the four kids shares a single life bar because of this. The kids will comment on game actions as they occur, with heavier profanity censored with bleeps. The kids will get angrier (and fouler) as their health depletes, until they finally give up on saving the town and go home.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/n64/South Park (USA)-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19981212T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Iguana Entertainment</developer>
		<publisher>Acclaim Entertainment, Inc.</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
		<players>4</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Wave Race 64 - Kawasaki Jet Ski (USA) (Rev 1).z64</path>
		<name>Wave Race 64</name>
		<desc>Wave Race 64 is sure to provide some of the most exciting racing you've ever experienced. Feel the pounding and crashing of the waves as you accelerate into straight-aways, whip around the marker buoys and go airborne on the jump ramps. Don't race alone! Challenge a friend!

* Nine challenging courses set in exotic locales - race conditions change and the wave action responds to the way both you and your opponents race.
* Take control in three different modes of play - Championship, Time Trials and Stunt Mode. 
* Game Pak memory will store your circuit progress, best times and custom sellings.
* Transfer best times and custom settings to a N64 Controller Pak to play at a friend's house.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/n64/Wave Race 64 - Kawasaki Jet Ski (USA) (Rev 1)-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19960927T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Racing</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Super Mario 64test.z64</path>
		<name>Super Mario 64test</name>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20220116T200437</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Donkey Kong 64 (USA)test.z64</path>
		<name>Donkey Kong 64 (USA)test</name>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20220116T200524</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Donkey Kong 64 (USA).z64</path>
		<name>Donkey Kong 64</name>
		<desc>K. Rool has ape-napped the Kongs!

Can Donkey Kong rescue his friends, reclaim the Golden Bananas and save his homeland from certain doom? Take out some Kremlings with Chunky's Pineapple Launcher or Lanky's Trombone. Float through the air using Tiny's Pony Tail Twirl. Even Rocket to the sky with Diddy's Jetbarrel!

-Don't forget the mini-games! Challenge a seal to a race around the lagoon, go on a crazy mine cart ride, and be on the lookout for a blast from the past...

-Four players can join in on super split-screen action or duke it out in a single-screen free-for-all!

-Use of the required Expansion Pak (included) allows incredible real-time lighting effects and massive environments.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/n64/Donkey Kong 64 (USA)-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19991122T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Rare, Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Adventure, Puzzle, Platform</genre>
		<players>4</players>
		<playcount>2</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20220116T202405</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Banjo-Kazooie (USA) (Rev 1).z64</path>
		<name>Banjo-Kazooie</name>
		<desc>Action and Puzzles and Bears, Oh My!

Trouble brews when Gruntilda the witch captures the unbearably beautiful cub, Tooty. But before the grisly hag can steal the bear's good looks, big brother Banjo and his fine-feathered friend, Kazooie, join forces to stop her. Combining their 24 moves and special powers, Banjo and Kazooie will fend off armies of beasts. Bear and bird must hunt down the 100 puzzle pieces and 900 musical notes that will ultimately lead them to Gruntilda. However, miles of swamp, desert and snow and one bear of an adventure stand in their way.

-Soar over islands to scout out buried treasure.

-Brave past whirling blades in the belly of a mechanical shark.

-With some voodoo magic, transform into different creatures to gain special powers.

-Solve the puzzles of the ancients to unearth the cursed labyrinths.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/n64/Banjo-Kazooie (USA) (Rev 1)-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19980629T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Rare, Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Adventure, Puzzle, Platform</genre>
		<playcount>2</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20220116T205443</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Banjo-Kazooie.z64</path>
		<name>Banjo-Kazooie</name>
		<desc>Action and Puzzles and Bears, Oh My!

Trouble brews when Gruntilda the witch captures the unbearably beautiful cub, Tooty. But before the grisly hag can steal the bear's good looks, big brother Banjo and his fine-feathered friend, Kazooie, join forces to stop her. Combining their 24 moves and special powers, Banjo and Kazooie will fend off armies of beasts. Bear and bird must hunt down the 100 puzzle pieces and 900 musical notes that will ultimately lead them to Gruntilda. However, miles of swamp, desert and snow and one bear of an adventure stand in their way.

-Soar over islands to scout out buried treasure.

-Brave past whirling blades in the belly of a mechanical shark.

-With some voodoo magic, transform into different creatures to gain special powers.

-Solve the puzzles of the ancients to unearth the cursed labyrinths.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/n64/Banjo-Kazooie-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19980629T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Rare, Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Adventure, Puzzle, Platform</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Donkey Kong 64.z64</path>
		<name>Donkey Kong 64</name>
		<desc>K. Rool has ape-napped the Kongs!

Can Donkey Kong rescue his friends, reclaim the Golden Bananas and save his homeland from certain doom? Take out some Kremlings with Chunky's Pineapple Launcher or Lanky's Trombone. Float through the air using Tiny's Pony Tail Twirl. Even Rocket to the sky with Diddy's Jetbarrel!

-Don't forget the mini-games! Challenge a seal to a race around the lagoon, go on a crazy mine cart ride, and be on the lookout for a blast from the past...

-Four players can join in on super split-screen action or duke it out in a single-screen free-for-all!

-Use of the required Expansion Pak (included) allows incredible real-time lighting effects and massive environments.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/n64/Donkey Kong 64-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19991122T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Rare, Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Adventure, Puzzle, Platform</genre>
		<players>4</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Paper Mario.z64</path>
		<name>Paper Mario</name>
		<desc>Mario pals around in an all-new action adventure! Mario's back in his first adventure since Super Mario 64, and this time, Bowser's bent on preventing a storybook ending. When Princess Peach is kidnapped, Mario plots to rescue the seven Star Spirits and rid the Mushroom Kingdom of Koopa's cruel cohorts. As he travels from the tropical jungles of Lavalava Island to the frosty heights of Shiver Mountain, he'll meet up with seven all-new companions... and he'll need help from each one or there'll be no happily ever after.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/n64/Paper Mario-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20010205T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Intelligent Systems Co., Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Role-Playing</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Quest 64.z64</path>
		<name>Quest 64</name>
		<desc>Celtland has been cast into chaos by the theft of Eletale's Book. This mystical volume contains the secrets of the Spirit Tamers. Control Brian, a magician's apprentice, as he explores the expansive countryside and villages on his quest. If he does not reclaim the book, the Kingdom of Celtland will be cast into darkness forever.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/n64/Quest 64-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19980611T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Imagineer</developer>
		<publisher>THQ</publisher>
		<genre>Role-Playing</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./South Park.z64</path>
		<name>South Park</name>
		<desc>Single player takes the form of a "Story" mode divided into five episodes and fifteen linear levels. The player will face weak minions (which change based on the episode), plus occasional sub-bosses which will try to escape into town. The final level is devoted to a unique boss fight. Players use quirky weapons ranging from infinite yellow snowballs to cow launchers and toxic Terrance and Phillip dolls. Every weapon has a secondary fire, and players switch between the four main characters when they switch weapons - each of the four kids shares a single life bar because of this. The kids will comment on game actions as they occur, with heavier profanity censored with bleeps. The kids will get angrier (and fouler) as their health depletes, until they finally give up on saving the town and go home.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/n64/South Park-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19981212T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Iguana Entertainment</developer>
		<publisher>Acclaim Entertainment, Inc.</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
		<players>4</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Wave Race 64.z64</path>
		<name>Wave Race 64</name>
		<desc>Wave Race 64 is sure to provide some of the most exciting racing you've ever experienced. Feel the pounding and crashing of the waves as you accelerate into straight-aways, whip around the marker buoys and go airborne on the jump ramps. Don't race alone! Challenge a friend!

* Nine challenging courses set in exotic locales - race conditions change and the wave action responds to the way both you and your opponents race.
* Take control in three different modes of play - Championship, Time Trials and Stunt Mode. 
* Game Pak memory will store your circuit progress, best times and custom sellings.
* Transfer best times and custom settings to a N64 Controller Pak to play at a friend's house.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/n64/Wave Race 64-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19960927T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Racing</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./The Legend of Zelda - Majora's Mask.z64</path>
		<name>The Legend of Zelda - Majora's Mask</name>
		<playcount>2</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20220116T213345</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./The Legend of Zelda - Ocarina of Time.z64</path>
		<name>The Legend of Zelda - Ocarina of Time</name>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20220116T213303</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Duke Nukem 64.z64</path>
		<name>Duke Nukem 64</name>
		<desc>Duke Nukem's coming to get some! Prepare yourself to become the biggest, baddest, alien basher in the known universe - Duke Nukem; as you blast your way through the streets of LA out to an orbiting station, and onto the moon itself. Bag some aliens with over a dozen hi-tech weapons. 32 levels of non-stop carnage. Run, jump, crawl, swim, and jetpack your way through danger. Big weapons and bigger bosses for a fun-filled fragfest! Four-player, split-screen Dukematch action.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/n64/Duke Nukem 64-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19971031T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>GT Interactive</developer>
		<publisher>Eurocom Entertainment Software</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
		<players>4</players>
		<playcount>3</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20220116T220212</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Yoshi's Story.z64</path>
		<name>Yoshi's Story</name>
		<desc>Baby Bowser has taken the Super Happy Tree and cast a spell on Yoshi's world, turning it into the pages of a picture book.  The only Yoshis not affected by the spell were six hatchlings that were still protected by their shells.  It's up to them to reclaim the Super Happy Tree and restore happiness to the world.  That is the only thing that can break Baby Bowser's Spell!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/n64/Yoshi's Story-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19980301T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Adventure</genre>
		<playcount>4</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20220116T215353</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Super Mario 64.z64</path>
		<name>Super Mario 64</name>
		<desc>Mario is super in a whole new way! Combining the finest 3-D graphics ever developed for a video game and an explosive sound track, Super Mario 64™ becomes a new standard for video games. It's packed with bruising battles, daunting obstacle courses and underwater adventures. Retrieve the Power Stars from their hidden locations and confront your arch nemesis -- Bowser, King of the Koopas!

-Run freely in a grassy meadow, tip-toe through a gloomy dungeon, climb to the top of a mountain or take a swim in the moat!

-Leap head first into a watery painting and soon you'll be searching for the surface in an underwater realm!

-On-the-fly, 3-D rendered game play delivers the action of ruthless enemy attacks from every angle!

-Find the Caps that give Mario super powers, ponder the mysteries of the pyramid, you can even race Koopas for fabulous prizes!

-With the Nintendo 64 Controller and its analog Control Stick, Mario can crawl, kick down obstacles, swim, do reverse flips, and even stick the landing on his backwards somersault!

-Saved game information is stored for up to four players in memory.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/n64/Super Mario 64-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19960926T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Adventure, Puzzle, Platform</genre>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20220119T191654</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./007 - The World Is Not Enough (USA).z64</path>
		<name>007 The World Is Not Enough</name>
		<desc>Bond Is Back

Experience the intensity of being the world's top secret agent. Equipped with a full arsenal of Q-Lab gadgets and weaponry, you must be suave, resourceful and lethal as you carry out action-packed missions based on the blockbuster movie. Are you cool under pressure? Deadly when necessary? Of course you are - you're Bond... James Bond 

• Bond's Best Missions! Battle through 14 dangerous levels with dynamic objectives based on your skill level.
• Over 40 Q-Lab Gadgets and Weapons! Bond's P2K, X-Ray Glasses, Watch Stunner, and many more.
• Action-packed Multiplayer! Customizable multiplayer modes for 1 to 4 players plus AI controlled bots.
• Authentic Dialogue! Interact with you favorite characters and experience movie-like 3D cinematics with full speech.
• Expansion Pak Support for enhanced graphics and visual effects.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/n64/007 - The World Is Not Enough (USA)-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20001017T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Eurocom</developer>
		<publisher>Electronic Arts</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Shooter</genre>
		<players>4</players>
		<playcount>2</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20220202T184543</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./BattleTanx - Global Assault (USA).z64</path>
		<name>BattleTanx: Global Assault</name>
		<desc>On January 13, 2006, a Queenlord, Cassandra, is spying on Griffin Spade's family, telling her troops to kidnap Griffin's son Brandon and kill everyone else. Griffin and his army manage to push back the invaders, but Cassandra soon turns the tables by mind-controlling Griffin's own army. Griffin and Madison manage to escape San Francisco and begin chasing Cassandra across the United States, eventually cornering her in Washington, D.C.. Cassandra, however, escapes with Brandon to Great Britain; Griffin and Madison follow. They build a new army in Europe, and chase Cassandra through England, France and Germany. While in Paris, they discover Cassandra released the virus in 2001 to kill every female on Earth who didn't have the power of the Edge.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/n64/BattleTanx - Global Assault (USA)-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19991012T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>3DO</developer>
		<publisher>3DO</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>4</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Bomberman 64 (USA).z64</path>
		<name>Bomberman 64</name>
		<desc>The evil Altair is using the Omni Cube to drain the energy from Planet Bomber. With the aid of a mysterious helper, you must defeat Altair, and restore peace to Planet Bomber. In the Adventure mode, guide Bomberman through 24 areas of perilous conflict. Battle Altair's sinister allies, destroy their bases and put an end to the insane attack. The multi-player Battle mode offers endless hours of explosive action. Use the standard Bomberman character or create a custom one and save it to an N64 Controller Pak.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/n64/Bomberman 64 (USA)-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19971201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Hudson Entertainment, Inc.</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>4</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Extreme-G (USA).z64</path>
		<name>Extreme-G</name>
		<desc>Extreme-G is set in the distant future where Earth is a mere wasteland.  From their new found planet the human colonists watch with joy as their remote controlled power-bikes wreak havoc through their ancient cities.  There is only one winner, the first to cross the line… or the last to survive.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/n64/Extreme-G (USA)-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19970930T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Probe Entertainment</developer>
		<publisher>Acclaim Entertainment, Inc.</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Racing, Shooter, Sports</genre>
		<players>4</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./F-Zero X (USA).z64</path>
		<name>F-Zero X</name>
		<desc>It's you against 29 other machines competing for the title of F-Zero X Champion. You're racing at speeds of over 1,000 km/h high above the atmosphere. Your competition comes from every corner of the galaxy and won't shed a tear at the thought of smashing you off the track. With four-player simultaneous gameplay and the Rumble Pak accessory, you have the fastest racing game on the N64 system!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/n64/F-Zero X (USA)-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19981026T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Racing</genre>
		<players>4</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Gauntlet Legends (USA).z64</path>
		<name>Gauntlet Legends</name>
		<desc>In ages past, a corrupt mage named Garm used a set of Runestones to summon a demon named Skorne (It is not stated what Garm intended to use Skorne for; however, as Gauntlet Legends introduces Garm as a "greedy young mage", it can be assumed he wanted Skorne for his own personal gain.) However, Skorne crushed Garm and imprisoned his soul in the Underworld. Skorne, fearing the power of the Runestones, scattered them throughout the four realms, so that they could never be used against him. The player(s) must defeat the end bosses of each of the four realms to obtain the four golden keys which allow access to Skorne's temple. While traveling through each realm, he/she/they must also collect the Thirteen Runestones from where they have been scattered. The complete set of Runestones allows him/her/them to pursue Skorne to the Underworld in order to finally destroy him. The players must find 3 rune stones on each kingdom in order to defeat Skorne in the Underworld, and of course 1 from the battle grounds.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/n64/Gauntlet Legends (USA)-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19990831T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Atari Games</developer>
		<publisher>Midway Games</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>4</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./GoldenEye 007 (USA).z64</path>
		<name>GoldenEye 007</name>
		<desc>You are Bond, James Bond.

You are assigned to covert operations connected with the GoldenEye weapons satellite.  M will brief you on your mission and objectives from London.  Q Branch will support your efforts with a plentiful supply of weapons and gadgets.  Moneypenny offers you light-hearted best wishes and you’re off!

Your mission begins in the heavily guarded chemical warfare facility at the Byelomorye Dam in the USSR.  Look and shoot in any direction as you navigate 12 interactive 3-D environments.  Use stealth and force as you see fit in matters of international security.  Consider the military personnel expendable.  You are licensed to kill!

* Exciting 3-D environments.
* Highly intelligent enemies!
* Numerous Q gadgets and weapons!
* Battery-backed memory saves game progress!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/n64/GoldenEye 007 (USA)-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19970825T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Rare, Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Adventure, Shooter, Stealth</genre>
		<players>4</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Jet Force Gemini (USA).z64</path>
		<name>Jet Force Gemini</name>
		<desc>The insect invasion has begun.

The galaxy is being infested by the evil Mizar and his horde of Drones. Already, the planet of Goldwood has been subjugated and the peaceful Tribals enslaved. With an arsenal of mega-weapons at their disposal, the Jet Force Gemini team must travel in search of Mizar's lair - rescuing Tribals and splattering Drones along the way. But can Juno, Vela and their faithful dog, Lupus, exterminate the deadly threat before it's too late?

+ " The game also includes a multiplayer mode where two to four players can compete in traditional deathmatch games. " -Wikipedia</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/n64/Jet Force Gemini (USA)-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19991011T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Rare, Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Rare, Ltd.</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Adventure, Shooter</genre>
		<players>4</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Legend of Zelda, The - Ocarina of Time.z64</path>
		<name>The Legend of Zelda: Ocarina of Time</name>
		<desc>Ganondorf, the evil King of Thieves, is on the move, threatening the peaceful land of Hyrule.  He is determined to steal his way into the legendary Sacred Realm in hopes of harnessing the power of the mythical Triforce.  As the young hero Link, it is your destiny to thwart Ganondorf’s evil schemes.  Navi, your guardian fairy, will guide you as you venture through the many regions of Hyrule, from the volcanic caves of Death Mountain to the treacherous waters of Zora’s Domain.  Before you complete this epic quest, you’ll delve into deadly dungeons, collect weapons of great power and learn the spells you need to conquer the most irresistible force of all-time.

• The immersive storyline and environments draw players into an amazing 3D world.
• Time travel allows you to play as Link in different stages of his life.
• New gameplay features include a unique targeting system and 1st and 3rd person perspectives.
• Up to three games can be saved simultaneously to memory!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/n64/Legend of Zelda, The - Ocarina of Time-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19981123T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo EAD</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Adventure, Role-Playing, Puzzle, Platform</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Legend of Zelda,The - Majora's Mask.z64</path>
		<name>The Legend of Zelda: Majora's Mask</name>
		<desc>Link's all-new epic adventure lands him in the mystical world of Termina, where ever-present clocks count down the hours until a menacing moon falls from the sky above. When his horse and Ocarina are stolen by a strange, masked figure, Link embarks on an urgent quest to solve the mystery of the moon, save the world from destruction, and find his way back to the peaceful land of Hyrule.

-Link transforms before your eyes -Over 20 magical masks give Link powers and abilities he’s never had before! Watch him transform into hapless Deku Child, a mighty Gordon hero and a legendary Zora guitarist.

-Race against time -Characters and events flow with the hours of the day. Set your own schedule and even alter time itself in a race to stop the moon and save the world!

-Panoramic environments! Powered-up action battles! Fully interactive characters and events! Experience gorgeous rendered landscapes, swarms of attacking enemies and a deep, engrossing world of wonders with the power of the N64 Expansion Pak.
</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/n64/Legend of Zelda,The - Majora's Mask-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20001026T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Adventure, Role-Playing, Puzzle</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Perfect Dark (USA) (Rev 1).z64</path>
		<name>Perfect Dark</name>
		<desc>Step into the Dark... As Carrington Institute's most promising new Agent, Joanna Dark must uncover the truth behind the dataDyne Corporation's recent technological breakthroughs - breakthroughs which could have serious consequences for mankind.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/n64/Perfect Dark (USA) (Rev 1)-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20000522T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Rare, Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Rare, Ltd.</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Shooter, Stealth</genre>
		<players>4</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Star Fox 64.z64</path>
		<name>Star Fox 64</name>
		<desc>The Lylat system has been invaded! Join Fox McCloud and his Star Fox team as they fight to save the galaxy from the clutches of the evil Andross. Travel to many different 3-D worlds. Battle the enemy in the air and on the ground and listen in as Fox McCloud interacts with a cast of characters.

See how it feels to feel what you see! The N64 Rumble Pak controller accessory instantly transmits all the bumps and blasts during the action. It’s a new jolt to your game play experience!

-N64 Rumble Pak controller accessory and batteries included!

-Four Players compete simultaneously in Vs. mode!

-Game Pak memory saves the top 10 scores!

-Outstanding cinema scenes tell the Star Fox saga!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/n64/Star Fox 64-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19970630T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Adventure, Shooter</genre>
		<players>4</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Star Wars Episode I - Racer (USA).z64</path>
		<name>Star Wars Episode I: Racer</name>
		<desc>Join Jedi-to-be Anakin Skywalker in the Star Wars race of your life! Relive all the thrills and excitement of the Podracer sequence from Star Wars: Episode I. Hang on tight - with afterburners on, Podracers max out at a simulated 600 mph! Race in furious competition against more than 21 opponents! Take on over 21 tracks in 8 unique worlds. Avoid hazards such as methane lakes, meteor showers and Tusken Raiders! Featuring spectacular 3D environments!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/n64/Star Wars Episode I - Racer (USA)-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19990518T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>LucasArts Entertainment Company LLC</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Racing</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Super Smash Bros.z64</path>
		<name>Super Smash Bros.</name>
		<desc>It's a Bumpin', Bruisin', Brawlin' Bash!

The many worlds of Nintendo collide in the ultimate showdown of strength and skill! Up to four players can choose their favorite characters - complete with signature attacks - and go at it in Team Battles and Free-For-Alls. Or venture out on your own to conquer the 14 stages in single-player mode. Either way, Super Smash Bros. is a no-holds-barred action-fest that will keep you coming back for more!

-Plunge headlong into battle with your favorite Nintendo characters: Mario, Link, Donkey Kong, Pikachu, Samus, Yoshi, Kirby and Fox... plus 4 hidden characters!

-Characters use their own trademark attacks, such as Mario’s fireballs and Link’s sword.

-Grab a Fire Flower or Poké Ball and send your opponent sailing out of the arena.

-Compete in 8 different settings, each from a character’s home world and each with its own dangers.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/n64/Super Smash Bros-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19990426T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>HAL Laboratory</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Fighting, Platform, Party</genre>
		<players>4</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./007 The World Is Not Enough (USA).z64</path>
		<name>007 The World Is Not Enough</name>
		<desc>Bond Is Back

Experience the intensity of being the world's top secret agent. Equipped with a full arsenal of Q-Lab gadgets and weaponry, you must be suave, resourceful and lethal as you carry out action-packed missions based on the blockbuster movie. Are you cool under pressure? Deadly when necessary? Of course you are - you're Bond... James Bond 

• Bond's Best Missions! Battle through 14 dangerous levels with dynamic objectives based on your skill level.
• Over 40 Q-Lab Gadgets and Weapons! Bond's P2K, X-Ray Glasses, Watch Stunner, and many more.
• Action-packed Multiplayer! Customizable multiplayer modes for 1 to 4 players plus AI controlled bots.
• Authentic Dialogue! Interact with you favorite characters and experience movie-like 3D cinematics with full speech.
• Expansion Pak Support for enhanced graphics and visual effects.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/n64/007 The World Is Not Enough (USA)-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20001017T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Eurocom</developer>
		<publisher>Electronic Arts</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Shooter</genre>
		<players>4</players>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20220202T184733</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./007 The World Is Not Enough.z64</path>
		<name>007 The World Is Not Enough</name>
		<desc>Bond Is Back

Experience the intensity of being the world's top secret agent. Equipped with a full arsenal of Q-Lab gadgets and weaponry, you must be suave, resourceful and lethal as you carry out action-packed missions based on the blockbuster movie. Are you cool under pressure? Deadly when necessary? Of course you are - you're Bond... James Bond 

• Bond's Best Missions! Battle through 14 dangerous levels with dynamic objectives based on your skill level.
• Over 40 Q-Lab Gadgets and Weapons! Bond's P2K, X-Ray Glasses, Watch Stunner, and many more.
• Action-packed Multiplayer! Customizable multiplayer modes for 1 to 4 players plus AI controlled bots.
• Authentic Dialogue! Interact with you favorite characters and experience movie-like 3D cinematics with full speech.
• Expansion Pak Support for enhanced graphics and visual effects.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/n64/007 The World Is Not Enough-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20001017T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Eurocom</developer>
		<publisher>Electronic Arts</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Shooter</genre>
		<players>4</players>
		<playcount>2</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20220202T191013</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./BattleTanx - Global Assault.z64</path>
		<name>BattleTanx: Global Assault</name>
		<desc>On January 13, 2006, a Queenlord, Cassandra, is spying on Griffin Spade's family, telling her troops to kidnap Griffin's son Brandon and kill everyone else. Griffin and his army manage to push back the invaders, but Cassandra soon turns the tables by mind-controlling Griffin's own army. Griffin and Madison manage to escape San Francisco and begin chasing Cassandra across the United States, eventually cornering her in Washington, D.C.. Cassandra, however, escapes with Brandon to Great Britain; Griffin and Madison follow. They build a new army in Europe, and chase Cassandra through England, France and Germany. While in Paris, they discover Cassandra released the virus in 2001 to kill every female on Earth who didn't have the power of the Edge.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/n64/BattleTanx - Global Assault-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19991012T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>3DO</developer>
		<publisher>3DO</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>4</players>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20220202T191245</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Bomberman 64.z64</path>
		<name>Bomberman 64</name>
		<desc>The evil Altair is using the Omni Cube to drain the energy from Planet Bomber. With the aid of a mysterious helper, you must defeat Altair, and restore peace to Planet Bomber. In the Adventure mode, guide Bomberman through 24 areas of perilous conflict. Battle Altair's sinister allies, destroy their bases and put an end to the insane attack. The multi-player Battle mode offers endless hours of explosive action. Use the standard Bomberman character or create a custom one and save it to an N64 Controller Pak.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/n64/Bomberman 64-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19971201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Hudson Entertainment, Inc.</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>4</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Extreme-G.z64</path>
		<name>Extreme-G</name>
		<desc>Extreme-G is set in the distant future where Earth is a mere wasteland.  From their new found planet the human colonists watch with joy as their remote controlled power-bikes wreak havoc through their ancient cities.  There is only one winner, the first to cross the line… or the last to survive.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/n64/Extreme-G-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19970930T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Probe Entertainment</developer>
		<publisher>Acclaim Entertainment, Inc.</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Racing, Shooter, Sports</genre>
		<players>4</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./F-Zero X.z64</path>
		<name>F-Zero X</name>
		<desc>It's you against 29 other machines competing for the title of F-Zero X Champion. You're racing at speeds of over 1,000 km/h high above the atmosphere. Your competition comes from every corner of the galaxy and won't shed a tear at the thought of smashing you off the track. With four-player simultaneous gameplay and the Rumble Pak accessory, you have the fastest racing game on the N64 system!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/n64/F-Zero X-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19981026T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Racing</genre>
		<players>4</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Gauntlet Legends.z64</path>
		<name>Gauntlet Legends</name>
		<desc>In ages past, a corrupt mage named Garm used a set of Runestones to summon a demon named Skorne (It is not stated what Garm intended to use Skorne for; however, as Gauntlet Legends introduces Garm as a "greedy young mage", it can be assumed he wanted Skorne for his own personal gain.) However, Skorne crushed Garm and imprisoned his soul in the Underworld. Skorne, fearing the power of the Runestones, scattered them throughout the four realms, so that they could never be used against him. The player(s) must defeat the end bosses of each of the four realms to obtain the four golden keys which allow access to Skorne's temple. While traveling through each realm, he/she/they must also collect the Thirteen Runestones from where they have been scattered. The complete set of Runestones allows him/her/them to pursue Skorne to the Underworld in order to finally destroy him. The players must find 3 rune stones on each kingdom in order to defeat Skorne in the Underworld, and of course 1 from the battle grounds.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/n64/Gauntlet Legends-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19990831T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Atari Games</developer>
		<publisher>Midway Games</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>4</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Perfect Dark.z64</path>
		<name>Perfect Dark</name>
		<desc>Step into the Dark... As Carrington Institute's most promising new Agent, Joanna Dark must uncover the truth behind the dataDyne Corporation's recent technological breakthroughs - breakthroughs which could have serious consequences for mankind.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/n64/Perfect Dark-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20000522T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Rare, Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Rare, Ltd.</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Shooter, Stealth</genre>
		<players>4</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Star Wars Episode I - Racer.z64</path>
		<name>Star Wars Episode I: Racer</name>
		<desc>Join Jedi-to-be Anakin Skywalker in the Star Wars race of your life! Relive all the thrills and excitement of the Podracer sequence from Star Wars: Episode I. Hang on tight - with afterburners on, Podracers max out at a simulated 600 mph! Race in furious competition against more than 21 opponents! Take on over 21 tracks in 8 unique worlds. Avoid hazards such as methane lakes, meteor showers and Tusken Raiders! Featuring spectacular 3D environments!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/n64/Star Wars Episode I - Racer-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19990518T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>LucasArts Entertainment Company LLC</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Racing</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./BattleTanx Global Assault.z64</path>
		<name>BattleTanx: Global Assault</name>
		<desc>On January 13, 2006, a Queenlord, Cassandra, is spying on Griffin Spade's family, telling her troops to kidnap Griffin's son Brandon and kill everyone else. Griffin and his army manage to push back the invaders, but Cassandra soon turns the tables by mind-controlling Griffin's own army. Griffin and Madison manage to escape San Francisco and begin chasing Cassandra across the United States, eventually cornering her in Washington, D.C.. Cassandra, however, escapes with Brandon to Great Britain; Griffin and Madison follow. They build a new army in Europe, and chase Cassandra through England, France and Germany. While in Paris, they discover Cassandra released the virus in 2001 to kill every female on Earth who didn't have the power of the Edge.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/n64/BattleTanx Global Assault-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19991012T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>3DO</developer>
		<publisher>3DO</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>4</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./GoldenEye 007.z64</path>
		<name>GoldenEye 007</name>
		<desc>You are Bond, James Bond.

You are assigned to covert operations connected with the GoldenEye weapons satellite.  M will brief you on your mission and objectives from London.  Q Branch will support your efforts with a plentiful supply of weapons and gadgets.  Moneypenny offers you light-hearted best wishes and you’re off!

Your mission begins in the heavily guarded chemical warfare facility at the Byelomorye Dam in the USSR.  Look and shoot in any direction as you navigate 12 interactive 3-D environments.  Use stealth and force as you see fit in matters of international security.  Consider the military personnel expendable.  You are licensed to kill!

* Exciting 3-D environments.
* Highly intelligent enemies!
* Numerous Q gadgets and weapons!
* Battery-backed memory saves game progress!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/n64/GoldenEye 007-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19970825T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Rare, Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Adventure, Shooter, Stealth</genre>
		<players>4</players>
		<playcount>53</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20220206T204211</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Jet Force Gemini.z64</path>
		<name>Jet Force Gemini</name>
		<desc>The insect invasion has begun.

The galaxy is being infested by the evil Mizar and his horde of Drones. Already, the planet of Goldwood has been subjugated and the peaceful Tribals enslaved. With an arsenal of mega-weapons at their disposal, the Jet Force Gemini team must travel in search of Mizar's lair - rescuing Tribals and splattering Drones along the way. But can Juno, Vela and their faithful dog, Lupus, exterminate the deadly threat before it's too late?

+ " The game also includes a multiplayer mode where two to four players can compete in traditional deathmatch games. " -Wikipedia</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/n64/Jet Force Gemini-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19991011T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Rare, Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Rare, Ltd.</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Adventure, Shooter</genre>
		<players>4</players>
		<playcount>16</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20220206T212046</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Mario Kart 64.z64</path>
		<name>Mario Kart 64</name>
		<desc>Three… Two… One… GO! The signal light changes and you drop the pedal to the metal. Take on up to three friends in the split-screen VS games, or race solo in the Mario GP. Tell your friends to bring it on in the highly competitive Battle mode. Advanced features allow you to race with your “Ghost”. The driving data from your best run appears as a transparent character on the screen. No longer must you simply race against the clock -- you can actually race against yourself!

-Save your hottest Ghost data to a portable N64 Controller Pak™ (Sold Separately)

-Collect multiple power-up items!

-Twenty different courses -- 4 Cups with 4 courses each and 4 special Battle mode courses!

-Everyone’s favorite characters are back and gorgeously rendered, including two new additions, Donkey Kong™ and Wario™!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/n64/Mario Kart 64-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19970210T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Racing</genre>
		<players>4</players>
		<playcount>7</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20220206T213428</lastplayed>
	</game>
</gameList>
